他希望我们继承他的事业
Dad wants us to pick up where he left off.
拯救人们 猎杀恶鬼 家族使命
Saving people, hunting things. The family business.
你知道真相的 关于萨姆…
You know the truth about Sammy?
我早就知道了
I've known for a while.
你能预先看到人们的死亡？
You get premonitions of people about to die?
- 预见死亡？- 没错
- Death visions? - Yeah.
那个恶魔说为我制定了计划
The demon said he had plans for me.
- 你明白这是什么意思么？- 我不知道
- Do you have any idea what he meant? - No.
我要你看着萨姆 行吗？
I want you to watch out for Sammy, okay?
他有对你说什么吗？
Did he say anything to you?
没有
No.
这些话我不能对萨姆说 对他我得摆张扑克脸
Can't talk about this to Sammy. Gotta keep my game face on.
你在边缘 你一直紧绷着
You're on edge. You're erratic.
除了在打猎的时候 因为那时你只能感到恐惧
Except for when you're hunting, then you're downright scary.
事实是 我并不好受
The truth is I'm not handling it very well.
你无法控制情绪 还拒绝我的帮助
You're tailspinning, man. And you won't let me help you.
不不不 你不是想…
No, no, no. You're not gonna…
我发誓那东西不在我身上
No, I swear, it's not in me.
哦 上帝 我们都会死在这里
Oh, God. We're all gonna die.
- 也许他说的是实话 - 他不是原来的他 不再是了
- Maybe he's telling the truth. - He's not him, not anymore.
停下 停下 问她 问医生
No, stop. Stop it! Ask her! Ask the doctor!
- 告诉他那东西不在我身上 - 我… 真的…
- It's not in me! - I just…
我不知道
I can't tell.
不 求你 不在我身上
No, please. Don't, don't.
- 我发誓 我发誓 - 我别无选择
- I swear, I swear. - I got no choice.
不在我身上 不在我身上
It's not in me. It's not in me.
不在我身上
Don't. Don't.
求你
Please.
萨姆？
Sam?
[邪恶力量 第2季第9集]
继续向俄勒冈西- 224行驶
Continue on OR-224 west.
美国只有两个叫河格罗夫的城市
There are two towns in the U.S. named Rivergrove.
你怎么知道是俄勒冈州的那个？
How come you're so sure it's the one in Oregon?
墙上有幅画 画着火山湖
There was a picture of Crater Lake.
好吧 还有什么？
Okay, what else?
昏暗的房间 一些人 还有… 一个人被绑在椅子上
I saw a dark room, some people, and a guy tied to a chair.
然后我在他身上开了个枪洞？
And I ventilated him?
是的
Yeah.
你认为他体内有东西
You thought there was something inside him.
是什么？他被附身了么？我不知道
- A demon? Was he possessed? - I don't know.
你的预见每次都或多或少关系到那个黄眼睛恶魔
All your visions are tied to the yellow-eyed demon.
有没有梦见黑烟？我们有没有念驱逐咒？
Was there any black smoke? Did we try to exorcise him?
没有 你就这么毙了他
No, nothing. You just plugged him. That's it.
那我肯定有理由
I'm sure I had a good reason.
但愿如此
I sure hope so.
你什么意思？
What does that mean?
我是不会杀无辜之人的
I mean, I'm not gonna waste an innocent man.
- 我不会的 - 我从没说你会
- I wouldn't. - Never said you would.
- 好吧 - 好的
- Fine. - Fine.
我们还不知道将发生什么 但无论如何
We don't know what it is, but whatever it is…
那个人必然牵连其中 我们去找出那个人 看看会发生什么
that guy in the chair is part of it. Let's find him, see what's what.
- 好吧 - 当然
- Fine. - Fine.
他在那里
He was there.
- 早上好 - 早上好
- Morning. - Morning.
- 有什么能为你效劳的？- 当然
- Can I help you? - Yeah.
比利·吉本斯 弗兰克·别德 美国警官
Billy Gibbons, Frank Beard. U.S. Marshals.
- 有何贵干？- 我们在找一个人
- What's this about? - We're looking for someone.
一个年青人 二十岁出头
A young man, early 20s.
有一个小伤疤 在头顶这里
He'd have a thin scar right below his hairline.
- 找他做什么？- 没什么
- What'd he do? - Well, nothing.
事实上我们在找另一个人 但他也许能提供点线索
We're looking for someone else. We think this young man can help.
他没惹什么麻烦 至少目前还没有
He's not in any trouble or anything. Well, not yet.
我想你可能知道他的所在 军士长
I think maybe you know who he is, master sergeant.
我父亲曾经也在军队待过 他是下士
My dad was in the Corps. A corporal.
- 哪一连？- Echo- 2- 1
- What company? - Echo 21.
你能告诉我们么？
So can you help us?
杜安·唐纳有那么个伤疤
Duane Tanner's got a scar like that.
但我了解他 是个好孩子 洁身自好
But I know him. Good kid, keeps his nose clean.
哦 我绝对相信这一点 你知道他住哪吗？
Oh, I'm sure he does. Do you know where he lives?
他们一家人都住在Aspen路上
With his family, up Aspen Way.
谢谢
Thank you.
嗨
Hey.
- 「CROATOAN」？- 正是
"Croatoan"? - Yeah.
罗阿诺克 失落之地 想起来了么？
Roanoke? Lost colony? Ring a bell?
迪恩 你有在历史课上好好听过么？
Dean, did you pay any attention in history class?
当然 全球的战争枪声 议案如何变成法律
Yeah. The shot heard around the world, how bills become laws.
你说的不是学校（教的） 是「校舍摇滚」（教的）
That's not school. That's Schoolhouse Rock!
管它呢
Whatever.
罗阿诺克是英国在美洲建立的首个殖民地 在十六世纪后期
Roanoke was one of the first English colonies in America, late 1500s.
哦 对 对 对 我记得
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, I do remember that.
整个地方只留下了刻在树上的这个词
The only thing they left behind was a single word carved in a tree.
- 「CROATOAN」 - 是
- Croatoan. - Yeah.
没错 有很多种猜测 印第安人突袭 瘟疫…
And, I mean, there were theories, Indian raid, disease.
但没有人知道真相 就这么消失了
Nobody knows what really happened. They were all just gone.
我是说 一夜之间就消失了
I mean, wiped out overnight.
你不是真以为这里会发生这种事吧
You don't think that's what's going on here?
无论如何 我所预见的都不是好事
Whatever I saw in my head, it sure wasn't good.
但这怎么会有这个词呢？
But what do you think could do that?
好吧 诚如我所说
Well, I mean, like I said.
你的预见多少关系到那个黄眼恶魔 所以…
all your weirdo visions are always tied to the yellow-eyed demon somehow, so…
我们得找帮手 鲍比·艾伦 也许
We should get help. Bobby, Ellen, maybe.
对 是个好主意
Yeah, that's a good idea.
我没有信号
I don't have a signal.
我也没有
I don't either.
电话线断了
Line's dead.
我得说
I'll tell you one thing.
如果是我要屠城 就会从切断电话开始
If I was gonna massacre a town, that'd be my first step.
- 找谁？- 嗨
- Yeah? - Hi.
我们想找 杜安·唐纳 他住这是吧？
Looking for Duane Tanner. He lives here, right?
- 他是我哥哥 - 能和他聊聊吗？
- He's my brother. - Can we talk to him?
- 他现在不在 - 知道他去哪了么？
- He's not here right now. - You know where he is?
当然 他去罗斯林河边钓鱼了
Yeah. He went on a fishing trip up by Roslyn Lake.
- 你父母都在吗？- 对 他们在里面
- Your parents home? - Yeah, they're inside.
杰克 是谁？
Jake, who is it?
美国警官 我们想找你儿子杜安
U.S. Marshals, sir. We're looking for your son Duane.
怎么 他没犯什么事吧？
Why? He's not in trouble, is he?
没有 我们只是想问他几个问题
No. We just need to ask him a couple routine questions.
他什么时候能回来？
When's he due back from his trip?
- 我不太清楚 - 也许你夫人知道
- I'm not sure. - Well, maybe your wife knows.
你知道 我不知道 她现在不在
You know, I don't know. She's not here right now.
但你儿子说她在
Well, your son said she was.
- 我说过吗？- 她出去买东西了
- Did I? - She's getting groceries.
如果杜安回来 他上哪能找到你们？
When Duane gets back, there's a number where he can get you?
哦 不用麻烦了 我们晚点再过来吧
Oh, no, we'll just check in with you later.
有点诡异对吧？
That was kind of creepy, right?
- 欲盖弥彰之嫌 - 我们去看看
- Little too Stepford? - Bigtime.
没事的 妈妈 一点都不会疼
It's okay, Mom. It's not gonna hurt.
- 不 - 放下刀
- No! - Put it down.
有人吗？
Hello?
这里有人需要救治
Hello, we need a doctor here.
唐纳夫人 发生什么事了？
Mrs. Tanner, what happened?
- 她被袭击了 - 李医生？
- She's been attacked. - Dr. Lee?
没事
It's okay.
- 把她带进来 - 好
- Bring her in. - Okay.
嗨
Hey.
那是… ？
Is that…?
唐纳先生
Mr. Tanner?
他也遇袭了？
Was he attacked too?
不 事实上 是他发起的攻击 然后他被子弹射中了
No, actually, he did the attacking and then he got himself shot.
- 被射中了？- 没错
- Shot? - Yeah.
- 那你是谁？- 美国警官
- And who are you? - U.S. Marshal.
我想给你看徽章的 但是…
I'd show you my badge, but…
好吧 把他带过来
Oh, sorry. Bring him back here.
等一下 你说杰克帮了他？
Wait, you said Jake helped him?
你儿子杰克？
Your son Jake?
他们打我
They beat me.
把我绑起来
Tied me up.
- 我简直不敢相信 - 帕姆
- I don't believe it. - Pam.
贝弗莉 知道他们为什么那么做吗？
Beverly, you have any idea why they would act this way?
- 他们有毒瘾吗？- 当然没有
- Any history of chemical dependency? - No, of course not.
我不知道为什么
I don't know why.
前一秒他们还是我的丈夫和儿子
One minute, they were my husband and my son…
下一秒就像着了魔一样性情大变
and the next, they had the devil in them.
我们得谈谈
We gotta talk.
那两个人从骨子里变质了
Those guys were whacked out of their gourds.
你认为呢？魔鬼附身于众？
What do you think? Multiple demons, mass possession?
如果那样 受害的人应该有很多 天知道有多少
If it's a possession, there could be more. God knows how many.
也许人多的马上就能组成国会了
It could be like a frigging Shriner convention.
- 显然 - 这样消灭一个城市再简单不过
- Great. - That's one way to wipe out a town.
- 从内部着手 - 我不知道
- Take it from the inside. - I don't know.
我们没看到唐纳口中冒黑烟 也没有其他异常现象
We didn't see any demon smoke or any of the other usual signs.
我也不确定 但显然有东西把他们变成那样
Well, whatever. Something turned him into a monster.
知道么如果你当时把另一个解决了 我们现在就少一个隐患
If you'd taken out the other one, there'd be one less to worry about.
对不起 好吗我 当时犹豫了 迪恩 他还是个孩子
I'm sorry, all right? I hesitated, Dean. It was a kid.
不 「它」不是
No, it was an it.
这不是心慈手软的时候 萨姆
Not the best time for a bleeding heart, Sam.
- 病人怎么样了？- 糟透了
- How's the patient? - Terrible.
- 到底发生什么了？- 我们也不清楚
- What the hell happened? - We don't know.
- 但你们刚射杀了我的邻居 - 我们别无选择
- You just killed my neighbor. - Didn't have a choice.
也许吧 我去找警长 需要电话
Maybe, but we need the county sheriff. I need the coroner.
- 电话不通 - 我知道 我试过了
- Phones are down. - I know, I tried.
- 告诉我你们车上有无线电 - 是有
- Tell me you got a police radio. - We do.
但和其他东西一样失灵了
But it crapped out, like everything else.
我真不知道这到底是怎么回事
I don't understand.
- 最近的城离这多远？- 大约四十里外的响尾蛇
- How far to the next town? - About 40 miles down to Sidewinder.
好吧 我去那里看能否找到人来帮忙
I'll go there and see if I can find some help.
我的拍档会留在这里 保护你们
My partner will stick around, keep you guys safe.
保护我们什么？
Safe from what?
我回来的时候会告诉你
We'll get back to you on that.
什么？
What?
他体内淋巴细胞的含量异常高
His lymphocyte percentage is pretty high.
他的机体正在对抗某种病毒
His body was fighting off a viral infection.
- 是么？什么样的病毒？- 不能确定
- Really? What kind of virus? - Can't say for sure.
他的异常举动有可能是因为感染造成的吗？
Think an infection could've made him act like that?
有些病毒会造成痴呆
None that I've ever heard of.
但据我所知 尚无能引发暴力行为的病毒存在
Some can cause dementia, but not that kind of violence.
而且 我从没见过这种作用结果的血液样本
Besides, I've never heard of one that did this to the blood.
- 什么结果？- 血液里有种奇怪的残留物
- Did what? - There's this weird residue.
要我说 那是硫磺
If I didn't know better, I'd say it was sulfur.
硫磺
Sulfur.
- 嘿 - 抱歉 此路不通
- Hey. - Sorry, road's closed.
哦对 我看得出 出什么事了？
Yeah, I can see that. What's up?
- 隔离 - 隔离？
- Quarantine. - Quarantine?
- 为什么？- 不知道
- What is it? - Don't know.
这里附近有事发生
Something going around out there.
- 谁告诉你的？- 警长
- Who told you that? - County sheriff.
- 他在这吗？- 不在 他派我们来的
- Is he here? - No. He called.
你下车 和我们聊聊如何？
Say, why don't you get out of the car and we'll talk a little?
哦 作为魔鬼 你的确很帅 但我还没那么容易拜倒 抱歉
Oh, you're a handsome devil, but I don't swing that way, sorry.
相信你下车事情会好办很多 不会占用你很多时间的
I'd sure appreciate it if you got out of the car, just for a quick minute.
我绝对相信
Yeah, I bet you would.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你是说我丈夫和杰克都得病了？
Are you saying my husband and Jake had a disease?
那正是我们要调查的
That's what we're trying to find out.
在袭击过程中
Now, during the attack, do you remember…
你有直接接触到他们的血液吗？
did you have any direct contact with their blood?
哦 我的天
Oh, my God.
你不是认为我也感染了病毒吧
You don't think I've got this virus, do you?
贝弗莉说实话我不知道该怎么想
Beverly, I don't know what to think.
但如果你允许 我想取些你的血液样本
But with your permission, we'll take a blood sample.
- 手放在我能看见的地方 - 该死…
- Hands where I can see them! - Son of a
下车
Get out of the car!
Out of the car!
冷静点 大块头
All right, easy there, big guy.
- 放下枪 放下枪 - 你是他们中的一员吗？
- Put it down! Down! - Lower it now! You one of them?
- 不 你呢？你可能在说谎 - 不
- No, you? Could be lying. - No.
- 你也是 - 好吧 好吧
- So could you. - All right. All right.
我们可以站在这里讨论一整天 好吗？
We could do this all day, all right?
但我们在杀死对方以前 都先冷静一下
Let's take it easy before we kill each other.
- 大家都是怎么了？- 我不知道
- What's going on with everybody? - I don't know.
我的邻居 罗杰斯先生
My neighbor, Mr. Rogers…
- 你的邻居是罗杰斯？- 不再有了
- You got a neighbor named Mr. Rogers? - Not anymore.
他拿着柄短斧冲到我家 我把他放倒了
He came at me with a hatchet. I put him down.
他不是唯一的 所有人都变了
He's not the only one. It's happening to everyone.
我正要去医生的诊所 那里还有几个正常人
I'm heading to doc's place. There's some people left.
- 我要离开这里 - 这里无路可逃
- I'm getting out. - There's no way out.
他们封锁了桥 跟我一起走吧
They got the bridge.Come on
- 我不信你 - 好吧 那就待这儿 随你便
- I don't believe you. - Fine, stay here. Be my guest.
哦 这一程够轻松的
Well, this ought to be a relaxing drive.
如果我们都感染了怎么办？
What if we all have it?
- 如果我们都疯了呢？- 你要冷静
- What if we all go crazy? - You've gotta stay calm.
耐心等待 警官已经去寻求帮助了
All we can do is wait. The marshal's bringing help.
我不能再等了
I can't, I…
我得走了
No, I've gotta go.
等一下帕姆 你不明白
Pam. No, you don't understand.
我的男友在外面 我得确保他的安全
My boyfriend's out there. I gotta make sure he's okay.
嗨 等一下 拜托
Hey, hey, wait. Wait, please.
我知道你很不安 但是留在这里是最安全的
I know you're upset, all right? But it's safer if you stay here for now.
救援就快到了
Help is coming.
到了
There they are.
萨姆 开门
Sammy! Open up!
你们打过电话了么？路被封锁了
Did you guys get to a phone? Roadblock.
- 我们要单独聊聊 医生在里面 - 好吧
- I'm gonna have a word. Doc's inside. - All right.
外面发生什么了 迪恩？
What's going on out there?
不知道 我好像是「最后一个人」里的查尔顿·赫斯顿
I don't know. I feel like Chuck Heston in The Omega Man.
军士是我能找到的唯一的人
The sarge is the only sane person.
- 明白我们在对付什么了么？- 明白了 医生觉得可能是病毒
- What are we dealing with? You know? - Yeah, doc thinks it's a virus.
- 好极了 你呢？- 我想她是对的
- Okay, great. What do you think? - I think she's right.
- 是么？- 没错
- Really? - Yeah.
而且受感染者还企图 通过血液直接接触去感染其他人
The infected are trying to infect others with blood-to-blood contact.
还有 受病毒感染的血液中有硫磺成分
It gets better. The virus leaves traces of sulfur in the blood.
- 恶魔病毒？- 更像是恶魔细菌战
- A demonic virus? - Yeah, more like demonic germ warfare.
至少能解释为什么我会预见这些了
At least it explains why I've been having visions.
- 像圣经上写的大瘟疫 - 是啊
- It's like a Biblical plague. - Yeah.
你说得简直对极了 迪恩
You don't know how right you are, Dean.
我在爸爸的日记里
I've been poring through Dad's journal.
找到了关于罗阿诺克·科勒尼的记录
Found something about the Roanoke colony.
- 还有呢 - 爸爸对「CROATOAN」有自己的解释
- And? - Dad had a theory about Croatoan.
他觉得那是某个恶魔的名字 也叫做Daeva或者Reshef
He thought it was a demon's name, known as Dever or Reshef.
是疾病和瘟疫之魔
A demon of plague and pestilence.
那真是太好了 为什么选择此时此地？
Well, that's terrific. Why here? Why now?
不知道
I have no idea.
关键是 迪恩 天知道这瘟疫会传多远？
But, Dean, I mean, who knows how far this thing can spread.
我们得离开这里警告人们
We gotta get out of here. We gotta warn people.
他们逮住一个 在这里
They've got one. In here.
什么意思？那人的妻子… 她被感染了
What do you mean? The wife. She's infected.
我们得处理这事 不能放任她不管
We gotta take care of this. We can't leave her in there.
我的邻居们… 会越变越强
My neighbors, they were strong.
我们拖延越久 她的力量就越大
The longer we wait, the stronger she'll get.
你们想杀了贝弗莉唐纳？
You're gonna kill Beverly Tanner.
医生 可以治疗吗 某种治疗方法吗？
Doctor, could there be any treatment? Some kind of cure for this?
- 你能治愈吗？- 我甚至不知道那是什么东西
- Can you cure it? - I don't even know what it is.
她破门而出只是时间问题
I told you, it's a matter of time.
就让她在里面待着吧 你不能把她当动物那样射死
Just leave her there. You can't shoot her like an animal.
萨姆
Sam.
马克 你这是干吗？
Mark. What are you doing?
马克 是外面那些人
Mark, it's them.
他们把我关在这 还想杀了我
They locked me in here. They tried to kill me.
是他们被感染了 不是我
They're infected, not me.
求你了 马克
Please, Mark.
我们都认识那么久了 求你了
You've known me all your life. Please.
你确定她是其中之一？
You're sure she's one of them?
确定
Yeah.
哦 上帝 那上面有病毒吗？
Ah! Oh, God. Is there any on me?
- 我没事吧？- 你没事的 没事
- Am I okay? - You're clean. You're okay.
我们为什么还留在这里？拜托了 我们快离开这里吧
Why are we staying here? Please, let's just go.
不行 外面到处都是受感染的人
No, we can't, those things are everywhere.
我的天
Oh, God.
她说对了一件事 我们该想办法出去
She's right about one thing. We can't stay here.
我们得回罗德豪斯之类的地方去
We gotta get out, to the roadhouse or somewhere.
- 告诉人们即将到来的灾难 - 主意是不错
- Let people know what's coming. - That's a good point.
但是「活死人之夜」可没那么好结局
Night of the Living Dead didn't end pretty.
但我们也不能留在这里 听着 这里的居民大多都擅用来复枪
I'm not sure we got a choice. Folks up here are good with rifles.
所以就凭现在的火力 我们很容易被解决掉
Even with all your hardware, we're easy targets.
除非我们有… 炸药什么的
So unless you got some explosives…
我们可以自己做一些
We could make some.
嗨 让我进去 让我进去 求你了
Hey! Let me in! Let me in, please!
杜安·唐纳先生
It's Duane Tanner.
哦 感谢上帝
Oh, thank God.
杜安 你没事吧？
Duane, you okay?
- 这就是被我… - 没错
That's the guy that I. - Yeah.
这里还有谁在？
Who else is in here?
哦 等一下 小伙子
Hey, whoa, whoa, easy there, chief.
医生 给他来个全面检查 好么？
Hey, doc, give Duane a good once-over, would you?
帕姆？
Pam?
- 你们是什么人？- 这不重要
- Who are you? - Never mind who I am.
- 请吧 医生 - 好的
- Doc? - Yeah, okay.
杜安 你去哪了？
Duane, where you been?
我在罗斯林河那里钓鱼 下午才回来的
I was on a fishing trip up by Roslyn. I came back this afternoon.
正好看到罗杰·麦吉尔从家里被拖出来 被那些我熟识的邻居们
I saw Roger McGill being dragged out of his house by people we know.
然后他们竟然开始用刀割他
They started cutting him with knives.
我仓皇而逃 然后就一直躲在树林里
I ran. I've been hiding in the woods ever since.
有人见过我父母吗？
Has anybody seen my mom and dad?
尴尬
Awkward.
你在流血
You're bleeding.
- 那伤口是怎么来的？- 我只顾着逃跑 可能被树枝划到了
- Where'd you get that? - I was running. I must've tripped.
把他绑起来 那里有绳子
Tie him up. There's rope there.
- 等一下… - 坐下
- Wait-Sit down!
抱歉 杜安 他是对的 我们得谨防
Sorry, Duane. He's right. We gotta be careful.
谨防？防什么？
Careful? About what?
- 他们的血留到你身上没有？没有 什么意思？- 没有
- Did they bleed on you? - No. What the hell-? No!
医生 有办法证明吗？通过测试什么的？
Doc? Any way to know for sure? Any test?
- 我反复研究了贝弗莉的血液样本 - 我妈妈？
- I've studied Beverly's blood work. - My mom?
病毒有三小时的潜伏期
It took three hours for the virus to incubate.
硫磺要到那时才会出现
The sulfur didn't appear in the blood until then.
也就是说 我们没办法确定
No, there'd be no way of knowing.
在杜安被… 改变以前不行
Not until after Duane turns.
迪恩 我有话和你说
Dean, I gotta talk to you. Now.
在那张椅子上坐好
Sit in that chair over there.
这就是我梦里见到的 迪恩
This is my vision, Dean.
- 确实发生了 - 没错 我也看出来了
- It's happening. - Yeah, I figured.
你不能杀了他 不是现在 我们还不知道他是否被感染了
You can't kill him. Not yet. We don't know if he's infected or not.
我觉得那不用怀疑
I think we're damn sure.
那人不知从哪冒出来的 还那么巧划伤了腿 他全家都被感染了
Guy shows up out of nowhere. Got a cut, his whole family's infected.
我们应该把他绑起来 等待结果
We should keep him tied up and wait and see.
为了让他挣脱去感染其他人么？
For what? For him to hulk out? Infect somebody else?
不 谢了 我不能冒那个险
No, thanks, can't take that chance.
我也不希望 但这份工作就是那么难
I'm not happy about this. It's a tough job.
- 那才是最重要的 - 那对我们有什么好处？
- That's the point. - What does it buy us?
- 至少良心上能过得去 - 对我来说太晚了
- A clear conscience, for one. - Well, it's too late for that.
- 你是怎么了？- 什么意思？
- What's happened to you? - What?
你可能杀死一个无辜的人 却对此毫不在意
You might kill an innocent man and you don't even care.
你的行为不像你自己
You don't act like yourself anymore.
你知道吗 你就和外面那些人一摸一样
You know what? You're acting like one of those things out there.
嗨
Hey.
把该死的门打开 迪恩
Open the damn door. Dean.
不要那么做 迪恩 不要
Don't do it, Dean! Don't.
不不不 你不是想…
No, no, no. You're not gonna…
不 我发誓 我没被感染
No, no, I swear, it's not in me.
哦 上帝 我们都会死在这里
Oh, God. We're all gonna die.
也许他说的是实话
Maybe he's telling the truth.
- 不 他不是原来的他 不再是了 - 停下 停下
- No, he's not him, not anymore. Stop, stop it!
问她 问医生 我没被感染
Ask her. Ask the doctor. It's not in me!
我… 真的…
I can't tell.
不能确定
Please, don't.
求你了 不要 不要… 我发誓自己没被感染
Don't, please. I swear, it's not in me. It's not in me, I swear.
我发誓… 自己没被感染… 不要 不要
I swear, it's not in me. Don't. Don't.
我别无选择
I got no choice.
不
No.
该死
Damn it.
已经过了四小时了
It's been over four hours.
杜安的血液没有任何反应 我想他没有被感染
Duane's blood is still clean. I don't think he's infected.
没问题的话 我去把绳子解开了
I'd like to untie him, if that's all right.
当然
Sure, yeah.
你知道我会问你原因的
You know I'm gonna ask you why.
没错 我知道
Yeah, I know.
那么 为什么？为什么没杀他？
So, why? Why didn't you do it?
我们要更多的酒精
We need more alcohol.
你感觉怎么样 帕姆？
How you holding up, Pam?
很好
Good
一切都快结束了
It'll all be over soon.
事实上…
In fact…
我一直在等这一刻
I've been waiting for this the whole time.
- 等什么？- 和你独处的一刻
- For what? - To get you alone.
她的血流到他身上了
She bled on him.
他被感染了
He's got the virus.
医生 再检查一下他的血液 好吗？
Doctor, check his wound again, would you?
医生
Doctor.
你还要她检查干嘛？你亲眼看到了
What does she need to examine him for? You saw what happened.
她的血真的接触到你的伤口了？
Did her blood actually enter your wound?
- 当然接触到了 - 我们不能确定
- Of course it did. - We don't know for sure.
我们不能冒险 你知道我们该怎么做
Can't take a chance. You know what to do.
谁也别想朝我弟弟开枪
Nobody shoots my brother.
他反正不会当你弟弟多久了 那是你自己说的
He won't be your brother much longer. You said it.
- 谁也别想射谁 - 你可是曾想射死我的
- Nobody's shooting. - You were gonna shoot me!
- 如果你不闭上嘴我还会的 - 迪恩他们是对的
- You don't shut your pie hole, I might. - Dean, they're right.
我被感染了 把枪给我 我会自行了断的
I'm infected. Give me the gun and I'll do it.
- 休想 - 我不想变成魔鬼
- Forget it. - I won't become one of those things.
- 萨姆 我们还有时间 - 有时间做什么？
- We've still got some time-For what?
我理解那是你弟弟 我很抱歉 但我必须尽快解决这事
I understand he's your brother, I'm sorry. I gotta take care of this.
我说最后一遍 如果你敢动一下 死的就是你
I'll say this once. Make a move on him, you'll be dead.
你懂我吗？我的意思听明白了么？
You understand me? I mean, do I make myself clear?
- 迪恩 - 我们能怎么做？
- Dean. - Then what are we supposed to do?
离开这里 走吧
Get the hell out of here, that's what.
开我的车 你们有炸药 车里有武器
Take my car. You got the explosives. There's an arsenal in there.
你们俩也一起走吧 你们有足够的火力应付外面的人
You two go with him. You got enough firepower to handle anything now.
那你呢？
What about you?
迪恩 不 不要
Dean, no, no.
跟他们走 这是你唯一的机会
Go with them. This is your only chance.
- 你可别想那么容易摆脱我 - 不 他是对的 和我们一起走
- Not gonna get rid of me that easy. - No, he's right, man. Come with us.
好吧 你是自掘坟墓
Okay, it's your funeral.
对不起 谢谢你的帮助 警官
I'm sorry. Thanks for everything, marshals.
哦 事实上 我们不是警官
Oh, actually, we're not really marshals.
嗯… 噢
Um… Oh.
现在要是有副牌就好了 或者桌式足球也不错
Wish we had a deck of cards or a foosball table or something.
迪恩不要那么做
Dean, don't do this.
离开这吧
Just get the hell out of here.
没门
No way.
把枪给我 然后离开
Give me my gun and leave.
我说最后一次 萨姆 不
For the last time, Sam, no.
这是你做的最傻的事
This is the dumbest thing you've ever done.
我可不那么认为 还记得在Tampa遇到的那个服务生吗？
I don't know about that. Remember that waitress in Tampa?
迪恩 我被感染了
Dean, I'm sick.
我完了 但是你不必陪我去死
It's over for me. It doesn't have to be for you.
- 不是 - 真的 你可以继续下去
- No? - No, you could keep going.
谁说我想继续了？
Who says I want to?
什么？
What?
我累了 萨姆
I'm tired, Sam.
这工作我真的干累了…
I'm tired of this job.
这种生活…
This life.
肩上的沉重负担 老天 我真的累了
This weight on my shoulders. Man, I'm tired of it.
那怎样？你就准备那么放弃？
So, what? So you're just gonna give up?
难道你准备就这么毫不反击地赴死？
I mean, you're just gonna lay down and die?
- 听着 迪恩 我知道因为爸爸的事… - 你错了
- Look Dean, I know the stuff with Dad had-You're wrong.
不是因为爸爸
It's not about Dad.
- 当然 有一部分 但… - 那么是因为什么？
- I mean, part of it is, sure… - Then what is it about?
你们最好出来看看
You better come see this.
所有人都不见了 无影无踪 他们全部都消失了
There's no one. Not anywhere. They've all just vanished.
已经过了五小时了 你的血液没有任何异常现象
Well, it's been five hours and your blood's still clean.
我不明白 但你好像躲过一劫
I don't understand it, but you dodged a bullet.
但我确实接触到了病毒
But I was exposed.
- 怎么会没被感染？- 我不知道 但事实的确没有
- How could I not be infected? - I don't know, but you're just not.
我可以拿你的样本和唐纳的比对一下…
I mean, when you compare it with the Tanners' samples…
怎么会？
What the hell?
什么？
What?
他们血液里的病毒消失了
Their blood. There's no trace of the virus.
没有硫磺 什么也没有
No sulfur, nothing.
军士和我要离开这里 去南边
Doc, the sarge and I are getting the hell out of here, heading south.
- 你一起来吧 - 我会去响尾蛇那里
- You should come. - I'd better get over to Sidewinder.
找人过来调查 但愿他们相信我的话
Get the authorities up here, if they'll believe me.
保重
Take care.
他呢？
What about him?
他不会有事的 没有任何感染迹象
He's gonna be fine. No signs of infection.
嗨 不要那样看着我 我也毫无头绪
Hey, man, don't look at me. I got no clue.
我发誓 今夜我会因此失眠
I swear, I'm gonna lose sleep over this one.
为什么在此时此地？
I mean, why here? Why now?
所有人都去哪了？难道真的有人间蒸发？
Where the hell did everybody go? It's not like they just frigging melted.
为什么我对病毒免疫？
And why was I immune?
哦对 知道么 好问题
Yeah. You know what? That's a good question.
我开始感觉那才是 最需要回答的问题
You know, I'm already starting to feel like this is the one that got away.
你能在那边停一下吗？
Do you mind pulling over up ahead there?
没问题
All right.
我要打个电话 这的电话都不通
- I gotta make a call. - No phone out here.
我自有办法
I got it covered.
那是什么鬼东西？
What the hell is that?
结束了 结果会令你满意的
It's over. You'll be pleased.
我觉得 不需要再进行其他测试了
I don't think any more tests are necessary.
那个温彻斯特小子 绝对是免疫的 不出所料
The Winchester boy, definitely immune, as expected.
当然
Yes, of course.
没有任何证据留下
Nothing left behind.
昨晚
So… Last night.
你不准备告诉我
You wanna tell me what the hell you were talking about?
- 你想说什么吗？- 你什么意思？
- What do you mean? - What do I mean?
我什么意思？你说你对这份工作感到疲累
I mean, you said you were tired of the job.
而那不仅是因为爸爸的关系
And that it wasn't because of Dad.
- 别提了 - 不 决不可能
- Forget it. - No, I can't. No way.
当时我以为我们都会死 你不能抓着那时的话不放
I thought we were gonna die. You can't hold that over me.
你不要和我装糊涂
No, you can't pull that crap with me, man.
- 你有话想说 - 如果我说没有呢？
- You're talking. - And what if I don't?
那么我会一直追问你 直到你说为止
Then I guess I'll just have to keep asking until you do.
我不知道 老弟 也许我在想我们应该…
I don't know, man. I just think maybe we ought to…
去大峡谷看看
go to the Grand Canyon.
- 什么？- 没错 我们一直
- What? - Yeah, you know…
在全国来来回回
all this driving back and forth across country.
却从没去过大峡谷 也许我们可以去T。-J。-
I've never been to the Grand Canyon. Or we could go to TJ.
或者好莱坞… 看看是不是有机会上林赛·罗韩
Or Hollywood, see if we could bang Lindsay Lohan.
你纯粹胡说八道
You're not making any sense.
我就是想说我们得休息一下
I just think we should take a break from all this.
为什么我们要回到这种生活中来？
Why do we gotta get stuck with the responsibility?
为什么我们不能享受下生活？
Why can't we live life a little bit?
你为什么这么说？
Why are you saying all this?
不不不 迪恩 你是我哥哥 明白么？
No, no, no, Dean. You're my brother, all right?
所以 无论你肩负着什么责任 让我一起分担 哪怕就一点
So whatever weight you're carrying, let me help a little bit.
我不能 我答应过他
I can't. I promised.
- 谁？- 爸爸
- Who? - Dad.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
爸爸在死前
Right before Dad died…
告诉了我一些事情
he told me something.
一些关于你的事情
He told me something about you.
什么？
What?
迪恩 他跟你说什么了？
Dean, what did he tell you?